ILGWU. James Parrott papers, 5780/143
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILGWU. James Parrott papers
1980-1991
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Parrott, James.
5780/143
15.5 cubic feet
15 linear feet
Records
Correspondence, reprints, and congressional testimony of James Parrott, Executive Assistant to the President, International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Parrott's records consist primarily of subject files, many of which pertain to ILGWU organizing around proposed changes on the regulation of homework, as well as around the New York City's apparel industry, especially the Garment Industry Development Corporation.
5510299
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff
Date completed:
1998
EAD encoding:
Casey Westerman, 2003Cheryl Beredo, June 2011
Biographical / Historical
The International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union was founded in New York City in 1900 by mostly Socialist immigrant workers who sought to unite the various crafts in the growing women's garment industry. The union soon reflected changes in the sector and rapidly organized thousands of unskilled and semi-skilled women, mostly Jewish and Italian young immigrants. Exemplifying the "new unionism," the ILGWU led two of the most widespread and best-known industrial strikes of the early Twentieth Century: the shirtwaist makers' strike of 1909 in New York City and the cloak makers' strike of 1910 in Chicago. The union also tried to adapt to the fragmented and unstable nature of the industry. It adopted the "protocol of peace," a system of industrial relations that attempted to ensure stability and limit strikes and production disruption by providing for an arbitration system to resolve disputes.
The ILGWU exemplified the European-style social unionism of its founding members. They pursued bread and butter issues but provided educational opportunities, benefits, and social programs to union members as well. In 1919, the ILGWU became the first American union to negotiate an unemployment compensation fund that was contributed to by its employers. The ILGWU also pioneered in the establishment of an extremely progressive health care program for its members which included not only regional Union Health Centers but also a resort for union workers, known as Unity House. The Union also had an imaginative and pioneering Education Department which not only trained workers in traditional union techniques, but provided courses in citizenship and the English language.
David Dubinsky, an immigrant from Belarus who came to the US in 1911, provided strong leadership that led to unprecedented growth in the union during his presidency from 1932 to 1966. He led the union through successful internal anti-communist struggles, built on the ascendancy of industrial unionism by encouraging the formation of the Committee for Industrial Organization, and helped the union become an important political force in New York City and state politics, and in the national Democratic Party and Liberal Party as well.
In the period following the Second World War, the union suffered a decline in membership as manufacturers avoided unionization and took advantage of less expensive labor by moving shops from the urban centers in the northeast to the south, and later abroad. The ethnic and racial character of the ILGWU also changed as European immigrants were supplanted by Asians, Latin Americans, African- Americans, and immigrants from the Caribbean.
In July 1995 the ILGWU merged with the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union (ACTWU) at a joint convention, forming UNITE (Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees). At the time the new union had a membership of about 250,000 in the United States, Canada, and Puerto Rico.
Scope and Contents
Correspondence, reprints, and congressional testimony of James Parrott, Executive Assistant to the President, International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Parrott's records consist primarily of subject files, many of which pertain to ILGWU organizing around proposed changes on the regulation of homework, as well as around the New York City's apparel industry, especially the Garment Industry Development Corporation.
Conditions Governing Access
The ILGWU Records, except for publications and materials produced for publication, are restricted. Materials created prior to twenty years from the current date are open to researchers only with prior written permission from the Director of the Kheel Center; materials created during the past twenty-years are closed; the minutes of the General Executive Board are closed. For more information contact the Kheel Center.
Related Materials
5780. ILGWU records
General
"Permanent deposit"
Women's clothing industry -- United States; Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- United States; Clothing workers -- United States; Industrial relations -- United States; Parrott, James.; Parrott, James.; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union
5510299
- (TC)2 [folder 1 of 2], 1980-1988 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- (TC)2 [folder 2 of 2], 1980-1988 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- (TC)2 Literature, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- (TC)2 Board of Directors, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- (TC)2 [folder 1 of 2], 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- (TC)2 [folder 2 of 2], 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Cost of Trade Restrictions [folder 1 of 2], 1982-1985 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Cost of Trade Restrictions [folder 2 of 2], 1982-1985 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Canadian-US Free Trade [folder 1 of 2], 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Canadian-US Free Trade [folder 2 of 2], 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- The Multifiber Arrangement, Historical, 1961-1983 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Multifiber Arrangement and Predecessors, 1981-1986 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- United States Trade Representative. Labor Advisory Committee (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Textile Legislation, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Federal Mediation Conciliation Service, 1988-1991 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- National Planning Association, 1986-1989 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Uretek, Inc., 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- International Rescues Committee, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Economic Policy Council, Mazur, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Plant Closing, Massachusetts and Rhode Island, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Immigration, Sol. C. Chaikin, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Undocumented Workers, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Economic Policy Council, 1983-1985 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Plant Closings, Legislation [folder 1 of 2], 1977-1983 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Plant Closings, Legislation [folder 2 of 2], 1977-1983 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- UMWA Solidarity, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Textile Legislation [folder 1 of 2], 1985 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Textile Legislation [folder 2 of 2], 1985 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Textile Legislation [folder 1 of 2], 1986 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Textile Legislation [folder 2 of 2], 1986 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Textile Legislation, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Black Economic Project, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Center on National Labor Policy, 1980-1989 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Homework, Clerical, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Homework, Congressional Testimony [folder 1 of 2], 1986 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Homework, Congressional Testimony [folder 2 of 2], 1986 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Homework, Department of Labor Wage and Hour Division, Proposal, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Homework, Department of Labor Congressional Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Homework, Department of Labor Letters, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Homework, Department of Labor Enforcement, 1982-1986 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Homework, Department of Labor Enforcement. Knitted Outerwear, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Homework, Department of Labor Regulations, 1982-1986 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Homework, General Accounting Office Report, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Homework, ILGWU Campaign, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Homework, Comment ILGWU, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Homework, ILGWU, 1981-1985 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Homework, Comment ILGWU, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Homework, Department of Labor and ILGWU Comments, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Homework, Department of Labor and ILGWU Meetings, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Homework, ILGWU Materials "Federationist", 1986 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Homework, ILGWU Materials, Newspapers, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Homework, ILGWU Materials-Question and Answer, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Homework, "It's Your Business" TV Program, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Homework, News, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Homework, News, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Homework, News, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Homework, Press Kits, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Homework, Pro-Press Conference, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Homework, Task Force [folder 1 of 2], 1986 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Homework, Task Force [folder 2 of 2], 1986 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Homework, Task Force Outreach, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Homework Statements, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Labor and Investments, Pension Funds, 1983-1992 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- New York City Comptroller Holtzman, 1990-1992 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Ridgewood Local Development Corporation, 1986-1989 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Regional Plan Association, 1988-1990 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Port Authority, 1984-1990 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Reference Point, 1988-1991 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Council for American Fashion, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Council for American Fashion [folder 1 of 2], 1989 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Council for American Fashion [folder 2 of 2], 1989 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Council for American Fashion, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Lehigh Valley Project Proposal, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Industrial Cooperation Council Apparel Project [folder 1 of 3], 1988-1991 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Industrial Cooperation Council Apparel Project [folder 2 of 3], 1988-1991 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Industrial Cooperation Council Apparel Project [folder 3 of 3], 1988-1991 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Industrial Cooperation Council Garment Industry Study Background [folder 1 of 2], 1987 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Industrial Cooperation Council Garment Industry Study Background [folder 2 of 2], 1987 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- New York State District Training and Child Care, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Garment Industry Advisory Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Garment Industry Advisory Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Garment Industry Advisory Committee, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Garment Industry Advisory Committee [folder 1 of 2], 1990 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Garment Industry Advisory Committee [folder 2 of 2], 1990 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Garment Industry Advisory Council Registration List, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Commercial Rent Control, New York City, 1985-1988 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- AFL-CIO Donahue, 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- AFL-CIO Education Update, 1990-1992 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- AFL-CIO Free Trade Union Institute, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- AFL-CIO Kirkland, 1988-1990 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- AFL-CIO Library, 1985-1990 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- AFL-CIO Reprints, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- AFL-CIO "Reviews the Issues" Reports, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- AIDS Materials, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- A. Philip Randolph Institute, 1988-1992 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- "All Labor Letter", 1986-1992 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Asia Society (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Bronx Economic Development, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- American Labor History Materials, 1979-1982 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Center for Labor Management Policy [folder 1 of 2], 1988-1992 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Center for Labor Management Policy [folder 2 of 2], 1988-1992 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Center for Public Integrity, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Chronicle Guidance Publications Inc., 1989 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Citizens for Justice, 1989-1991 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Civil Rights, 1982-1985 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Coalition of Labor Union Women, 1988-1991 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Community Service Society, New York City, 1988-1992 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Conference Board, 1985-1986 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Conference Board, 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Congressional Caucus for Women's Issues, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Javits Convention Center, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Elderly, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- English Only, 1989-1990 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- European Community Integration, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Ralph Fasanella, 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Federal Reserve Research Library, 1986-1990 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- California Industry, 1985-1989 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- El Paso [folder 1 of 2], 1990 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- El Paso [folder 2 of 2], 1990 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Organizing Materials [folder 1 of 2], 1987-1991 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Organizing Materials [folder 2 of 2], 1987-1991 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Jobs with Justice [folder 1 of 2], 1991-1992 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Jobs with Justice [folder 2 of 2], 1991-1992 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Strike Preparation [folder 1 of 2], 1990 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Strike Preparation [folder 2 of 2], 1990 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- South Africa, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Negotiations Preparation, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Bargaining, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Strike Preparation Task Force Report, 1990-1991 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Strike Preparation Task Force [folder 1 of 2], 1990-1991 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Strike Preparation Task Force [folder 2 of 2], 1990-1991 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Contract Language Task Force, 1990-1991 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Collective Bargaining, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Negotiations, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Negotiations, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Council for American Fashion, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Council for American Fashion, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Council for American Fashion. Miscellaneous, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Council for American Fashion. Manufacturing, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Council for American Fashion, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Women's and Children's Apparel Labor Management Committee, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Council for American Fashion. Public Relations, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Council for American Fashion. Steering Committee, 1989-1991 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Occupational Health Legal Rights Foundation, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Advanced Apparel Manufacturing Technology Reports [folder 1 of 2], 1989-1992 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Advanced Apparel Manufacturing Technology Reports [folder 2 of 2], 1989-1992 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Housing, 1985-1989 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Hunger, 1985-1989 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Apparel Technology [folder 1 of 2], 1988-1994 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Apparel Technology [folder 2 of 2], 1988-1994 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- LaRouche, 1986-1992 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Loft Board, New York City, 1985-1988 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Minimum Wage Reports, 1971-1983 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Minimum Wage, 1983-1987 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Congressional Research Service Talks. Minimum Wage, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Minimum Wage Miscellaneous [folder 1 of 2], 1981-1987 (Box 10)
- Minimum Wage Miscellaneous [folder 2 of 2], 1981-1987 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- National Unemployed Network, 1988-1990 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- NAACP, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- National Committee for Full Employment, 1985-1989 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- National Economic Commission, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- National Family Farm Coalition, 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- National Planning Association, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- New York City Air Pollution, 1990-1991 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- New York City Council [folder 1 of 2], 1988-1989 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- New York City Council [folder 2 of 2], 1988-1989 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Peter Vallone, 1988-1990 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- New York Labor Committee Against Apartheid, 1988-1989 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- National Union of Tailors and Garment Workers, Britain [folder 1 of 2], 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- National Union of Tailors and Garment Workers, Britain [folder 1 of 2], 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Triangle Fire, 1984-1991 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Industrial Union Department, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Technology and Public Policy, 1991-1992 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Industrial Union Department Technology Working Group [folder 1 of 2], 1991-1992 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Industrial Union Department Technology Working Group [folder 2 of 2], 1991-1992 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Trade and Global Business. Miscellaneous, 1986-1988 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Multibusiness Literature, 1983-1984 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- United Auto Workers District 65 Conference [folder 1 of 2], 1988 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- United Auto Workers District 65 Conference [folder 2 of 2], 1988 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- ILGWU Conferences, Hawaii [folder 1 of 2], 1988-1990 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- ILGWU Conferences, Hawaii [folder 2 of 2], 1988-1990 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Japanese Textile and Apparel Workers' Unions, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Miscellaneous Textile Materials, 1988-1990 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Commercial Rent, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Commercial Rent. Newspaper Clippings, 1986-1988 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Commercial Rent. Binding and Arbitration, 1987-1988 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Commercial Rent. Ad Hoc Coalition for NYC, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Commercial Rent. Councilman J. O'Donovan, 1987-1988 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- New York State Economic Development Zones [folder 1 of 2], 1991 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- New York State Economic Development Zones [folder 2 of 2], 1991 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Grovesville, NY Economic Development Zones, 1989-1991 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Economic Development Zones. Final Report, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Economic Development Zones, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Economic Development Zones Commission Correspondence, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Economic Development Zone Recommendations, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Economic Development Zone Programs [folder 1 of 2], 1990-1991 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Economic Development Zone Programs [folder 2 of 2], 1990-1991 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Bronx Project, 1990-1992 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Garment Center ILGWU Statements, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Garment Center News, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Garment Center News, 1988-1989 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Garment Center Zoning Study Final Report, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Garment Center Zoning Study. Harris Census, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Garment Center Zoning Study, ILGWU, 1986-1987 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Garment Center Zoning Study Press Conference, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Garment Center Zoning Study. Real Estate Analysis, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Garment Industry Development Corporation, 1990-1992 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Garment Center Zoning Study Testimony, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Garment Industry Development Corporation Annual Budget, 1987-1989 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Garment Industry Development Corporation. Annual Meetings, 1988-1989 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Garment Industry Development Corporation. Annual Reports, 1986-1991 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Garment Industry Development Corporation. By-Laws, Membership, Contracts, 1984-1988 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Garment Industry Development Corporation. ESL/CWE, 1991-1992 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Garment Industry Development Corporation. Industry Contributions, 1988-1990 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Garment Industry Development Corporation. News Articles, 1990-1991 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Garment Industry Development Corporation [folder 1 of 2], 1984-1987 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Garment Industry Development Corporation [folder 2 of 2], 1984-1987 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Garment Industry Development Corporation [folder 1 of 3], 1988-1989 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Garment Industry Development Corporation [folder 2 of 3], 1988-1989 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Garment Industry Development Corporation [folder 3 of 3], 1988-1989 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Garment Industry Development Corporation [folder 1 of 2], 1989-1990 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Garment Industry Development Corporation [folder 2 of 2], 1989-1990 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Garment Industry Development Corporation [folder 1 of 3], 1987-1988 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Garment Industry Development Corporation [folder 2 of 3], 1987-1988 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Garment Industry Development Corporation [folder 3 of 3], 1987-1988 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Export Program, 1990-1991 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Textile Industry, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Financing, Apparel, 1990-1991 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Maidenfom, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Retailers, 1990-1991 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Apparel Industry Trucking, 1990-1992 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Apparel Designers, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Associated Merchandising Corporation, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- New York State Enterprise Zones [folder 1 of 3], 1991 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- New York State Enterprise Zones [folder 2 of 3], 1991 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- New York State Enterprise Zones [folder 3 of 3], 1991 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Garment Industry Development Corporation. Proposal for Expanded City Assistance [folder 1 of 2], 1986-1988 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Garment Industry Development Corporation. Proposal for Expanded City Assistance [folder 2 of 2], 1986-1988 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Negotiations [folder 1 of 4], 1988 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Negotiations [folder 2 of 4], 1988 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Negotiations [folder 3 of 4], 1988 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Negotiations [folder 4 of 4], 1988 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Homework. Surveys [folder 1 of 2], 1989 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Homework. Surveys [folder 2 of 2], 1989 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Demands, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 14)